Post Office Arbitration Files 5739
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Buffalo, New York Local, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Seniority; Crossing Craft Lines. EX, AN, RC, A.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  RC. Cancelled.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Washington Region, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  Issue: Physical Disability--Light Work. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, New Jersey Area, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  Issue: Theft--Pilfering; Suspicion. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Woodbury Area Local, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Northern Virginia Area Local, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  Issue: Arbitrability--Timeliness; Falsification-- Application for Employment. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  RC. Settled.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  Issue: Arbitrability--Abandonment of Grievance. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Norfolk Local, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  Issue: Negligence and Carelessness--Employee Liability. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. Mail Handlers Union, Local No. 308, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  Issue: Improper Job Attitude--Insubordination. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. Mail Handlers Union, Local No. 305, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Management Rights; Past Practice. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. Mail Handlers Union, Local 308, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  Issue: Improper Personal Conduct--Off-Duty Misconduct. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. Mail Handlers Union, Local 305, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  Issue: Improper Personal Conduct--Off-Duty Misconduct; Drugs--Sale and Use. EX, AN, RC, SD.
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, Charleston, West Virginia Local, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  Issue: Union Security--Union Rights; Union Representatives and Business--Past Practice. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Syracuse Area Local, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Issue: Grievance and Grievance Procedure--Timeliness. EX, AN, RC. Withdrawn.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Philadelphia Local, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  Issue: Arbitrability--Abandonment of Grievance; Settlement in Grievance Procedure; Absences--Excuses. RC, AN, EX.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, National Capital Area Local, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Issue: Falsification--Absence Reports. RC, AN, EX.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Arlington, Virginia, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  Issue: Absences--Excessive. RC, AN, EX.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, John F. Kennedy Local No. 375, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  Issue: Theft--Company Product. RC, AN, EX.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Philadelphia, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Philadelphia, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Wilmington, Delaware, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Motor Vehicle Operators, Richmond, Virginia, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Change in Procedure. RC, EX, AN.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Mountaineer District, Charleston, West Virginia, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Issue: Absences--Weather Conditions. RC, EX, AN.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Capital District Local, Washington, D.C., 1983 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Issue: Grievance and Grievance Procedure--Timeliness. RC, EX, AN.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Allentown, Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Warrendale, Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Association of Post Office Mail Handlers, Division of LIUNA, Norfolk, Virginia, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Lynchburg, Virginia, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Harrisburg, Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Washington, D.C., 1983 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  Issue: Negligence and Carelessness--Carelessness. AN, EX, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Association of Post Office Mail Handlers, Division of LIUNA, Local No. 305, Richmond, Virginia, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Change of Duties. RC, EX.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Wilkes Barre, Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  Issue: Theft--Suspicion. RC, AN, EX.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Buffalo, New York, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Bellmawr, New Jersey, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Eastern Montgomery County Area Local, Devon, Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  Issue: Theft-- Employee Liability for Robbery. RC, EX, AN.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Wilmington, Delaware, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  Issue: Testing of Employees--Ability. RC, EX, AN.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Washington Area Local, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  Issue: Absences--Excessive. AN, RC, EX.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Association of Post Office Mail Handlers, Division of LIUNA, Local 308, Allentown, Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  Issue: Negligence and Carelessness-- Employee Liability. AN, EX, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Washington Area Local, Northern Virginia, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  Issue: Absences--Excessive. EX, RC, AN.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Northern Virginia Area Local, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  Issue: Improper Job Attitude--Leaving Plant or Work Area Without Permission. EX, RC, AN.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Norristown, Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  Issue: Schedules of Work--Change of Schedule; Weekend. EX, RC, AN.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Richmond, Virginia, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  Issue: Management Rights--Elimination of Jobs. NA, RC. Withdrawn.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Conway, Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  Issue: Working Conditions--Wash-Up Time. EX, RC, AN.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Wilmington Local, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  Issue: Physical Disability--Light Duty. AN, EX.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Wilmington Local, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  Issue: Vacations--Scheduling; Eligibility. RC, AN, EX.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Philadelphia Area Local, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  2 Cases: i) Grievance and Grievance Procedure-- Timeliness; Posting--Sufficiency. ii) Negligence and Carelessness--Investigation Procedure. RC, AN, EX.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Philadelphia Bulk Mail Center, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  Issue: Absences--Weather Conditions. RC, AN, EX.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Devon, Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Post Office Mail Handlers, Local 308, Cherry Hill, New Jersey, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Change of Duties. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Roanoke, Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Washington, D.C., 1983 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Erie, Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  Issue: Rates of Pay--Overpayment of Wages. RC, AN, EX.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Charleston, West Virginia, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  Issue: Rates of Pay--Wage Hold Back; Higher Classification, Claim for Pay of. RC, AN, EX.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Norfolk, Virginia, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Reading, Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Richmond, Virginia, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  Issue: Negligence and Carelessness--Neglect of Duty. RC, AN, EX.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Kensington, Maryland, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Issue: Arbitrability--Timeliness; Negligence and Carelessness--Employee Liability. RC, AN, EX.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Allentown, Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Issue: Absences--Permissive. RC, AN, EX.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Charleston, West Virginia, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Issue: Falsification--Company Records in General; Physical Disability--Benefits. RC, AN, EX.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Charleston, West Virginia, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Buffalo, New York, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Issue: Schedules of Work--Rest Breaks. RC, AN, EX.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Cherry Hill, New Jersey, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  Issue: Leaves of Absence--Vacation Extension. RC, AN, EX.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Huntington, West Virginia, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Northern Virginia, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Baltimore, Maryland, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Vienna, Virginia, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Charleston, W. Virginia, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  Issue: Absences--Excessive; Sick Leave and Sick Pay-- Administration of Plan. RC, AN, EX.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  Issue (for all 6 cases): Negligence and Carelessness--Employee Liability.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Baltimore, Maryland, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Assignment to Work Outside Classification. RC, AN, EX.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Roanoke, Virginia, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  NA, RC, Cancelled.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Motor Vehicle Craft, Richmond, Virginia, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  Issue: Classification of Jobs--Rates of Pay; Posting--Information Included. RC, AN, EX.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Hamburg, Harrisburg, Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Overtime; Qualifications. RC, AN, EX.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Conway, Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Buffalo, New York, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Norfolk, Virginia, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  Issue: Absences--Excuses. EX, AN, RC, A.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Charleston, West Virginia, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  Issue: Alcoholism, Drinking, and Intoxication-- Absences. RC, AN, EX.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Syracuse, New York, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  Issue: Classification of Jobs--Upgrading. AN, EX.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Buffalo, New York, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  Issue: Absences--Weather Conditions; Leaves of Absence. RC, AN, EX.
- Various USPS Agreements, 1971-1984 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 33)